let data = [
	{
		question:"You conceived a virus: do you sell it?",
		answers: ["Yes","No"],
		points: [3, 2]
	},
	{
		question:"You have to protect the NASA from cyber attacks, what do you do?",
		answers: ["I implement a password manager","I raise employee awareness"],
		points: [3, 2]
	},
	{
		question: "Do you send a phishing email to E-Corp (a NASA subsidiary) with your virus?",
		answers: ["Yes","No"],
		points: [4, 1]
	},
	{
		question: "Today, half of the company's computers have crashed: all the processors have imploded and caused a fire in the building, what do you do?",
		answers: ["I put water to put out the fire","I cut the company's power supply in an emergency"],
		points: [1, 4]
	},
	{
		question: "Do I get information about NASA employees?",
		answers: ["Yes","No"],
		points: [3, 2]
	},
	{
		question:"Do you update the company's VPS virus database?",
		answers: ["Yes","No"],
		points: [3, 2]
	},
	{
		question:"You develop a Trojan horse, do you want to publish it on the darkweb?",
		answers: ["Yes","No"],
		points: [4, 1]
	},
	{
		question:"Do you spend all day surfing hacking forums?",
		answers: ["Yes","No"],
		points: [2, 3]
	},
	{
		question:"Do you want to launch a DDoS attack on the delivery website of the local pizzeria?",
		answers: ["Yes","No"],
		points: [3, 2]
	},
	{
		question:"Although you have tried to protect the company, you are a victim of ransomware, what do you do?",
		answers: ["I disconnect all the power supplies and the company network","I wait for the director to pay the ransom"],
		points: [3, 2]
	},
	{
		question:"To protect your money do you convert it into Bitcoin?",
		answers: ["Yes","No"],
		points: [3, 2]
	},
	{
		question:"You have discovered a virus with interesting technology.",
		answers: ["You try to trace the hacker from it","You show it to the police and inform the director"],
		points: [4, 1]
	},
	{
		question:"You become more and more known in the hacking world and you decide to set up a team, do you attack the NSA?",
		answers: ["Yes","No"],
		points: [3, 2]
	},
	{
		question:"While surfing on darkweb forums, you heard about the creation of a suspicious team of hackers.",
		answers: ["You try to infiltrate them","You hire someone to track them down"],
		points: [3, 3]
	},
	{
		question:"A member of your team reported you to the authorities, what do you do?",
		answers: ["I move all my money to another bank and change my identity","I move to another country"],
		points: [4, 1]
	},
	{
		question:"You just got a promotion for your investment in the company. Do you invite your friends to celebrate this good news?",
		answers: ["Yes","No, I'm already invited to another party"],
		points: [3, 2]
	},
	{
		question:"Friends invite me to a party, do you go?",
		answers: ["Yes, no worries, my group will carry out an attack during the night","No, I could be attacked when I'm away"],
		points: [3, 2]
	},
	{
		question:"During your party you get a call from your boss who informs you that someone has entered the HoneyPot you set up.",
		answers: ["I continue the party because I am confident in my technology","I leave the party and drive back to work (drink driving again...)"],
		points: [4, 1]
	},
	{
		question:"You program a website that sells the NASA information, do you put up the information of your friend who works there?",
		answers: ["Yes","No"],
		points: [4, 1]
	},
	{
		question:"You hack the website and have access to the information of the hackers, do you want to reveal their identities to the public?",
		answers: ["Yes","No"],
		points: [4, 1]
	}
];
